What were some of the things you were
hoping to show today at Pro Day?
Um
I showed that I'm willing to do the
drills, you know, at combine I did
linebacker stuff today. I just wanted to
knock out the AS drills. Just do both,
make sure I do both of them cuz that was
my role last year, both of them. Yeah.
Do you feel like you offer that
versatility or do you want to
concentrate on one?
I think I offer that versatility, but
you know, it just depend on the
situation I'm going into. If I go to a
place and need me to focus on both, then
that's what I'm going to do cuz that's
what I did at Old State. If I need to
focus on one and perfect one, that'll be
that'll probably be even better. You
guys have a high concentration of talent
here today. Four guys projected to go in
the top 10. Um I don't know when that's
happened before, but what does that say
about the way Ohio State develops
players? Mhm.
Yeah, I think what what Ohio State does
is, you know,
they we they just do a lot of pouring
into us, you know, they pour into us a
lot.
And they give everything they got to us
from the from the strength staff, from
the nutrition staff, just from the
coaches and just becoming elite. They
play a huge part in that and then it
just take take all the guys committing
to it and I feel like everybody
you know, who is coming out, we all
committed to it, committed to the
program. Do you feel any anxiety going
into the draft? I mean, obviously
projected high, but is there any anxiety
about, you know, where you might go and
when you might go and those kinds of
things? Um
right now I wasn't even I ain't even
thinking about that right now. I'll be
honest, I was just thinking about the
Pro Day. So yeah, I wasn't even thinking
about that right now. Now I guess that
that's the next step. I guess I'm
thinking about that now, but yeah, no
anxiety right now. What's this process
been like for you to prepare for Pro
Day, prepare for the combine, you know,
doing interviews with teams? What's the
What's the process been like?
Uh for me it's just been it's been
exciting. Just, you know, taking
everything in, not trying to take none
for granted. Just enjoying every step of
it, you know, it's it's kind of flying
by, so you know, just taking everything
in and enjoying everything.